//Document ready function
//$(document).ready(function() {}


//Global variables

var numWins = 0;
var numLosses = 0;
//var audio = new Audio("LINK AN AUDIO FILE HERE");


//Trivia questions, possible answers, correct answer and correct/incorrect gifs.
var questions = {

	question1:
	{	actualQuestion:"What is Rick's last name?",
		answer1:"Williams",
		answer2:"Sanchez",
		answer3:"Mortimer",
		answer4:"Ricky",
		correctAnswer: answer2
	},

	question2:
	{	actualQuestion: "What fast food item that is no longer available is Rick trying to bring back?",
		answer1: "Angry Whopper",
		answer2: "Wendy's salad bar",
		answer3: "McRib",
		answer4: "McDonald's Mulan SzeChuan sauce",
		correctAnswer: answer4
	},

	question3:
	{	actualQuestion: "How does the family find out that Mr. Poopy Butthole isn't a parasite?",
		answer1: "Beth shoots him.",
		answer2: "They get an xray of him.",
		answer3: "Rick remembers where he is from.",
		answer4: "He pulls out his passport.",
		correctAnswer: answer1
	},

	question4:
	{	actualQuestion: "The original title of the show was called...?", 
		answer1: "Travelling through the Multiverse",
		answer2: "Gramps and Shorty",
		answer3: "The Real Animated Aventures Of Doc And Mharti",
		answer4: "Multidimensional Adventures",
		correctAnswer: answer3
	},

	question5:
	{	actualQuestion: "What other show does the coffee cup, notepad and pencil come from when they fly in through a portal?",
		answer1: "Ren and Stimpy",
		answer2: "He-man and the Masters of the Universe",
		answer3: "Courage the Cowardly Dog",
		answer4: "Gravity Falls",
		correctAnswer: answer4
	},

	question:
	{	actualQuestion: "How does Morty's game of Roy end?",
		answer1: "He falls off a ladder in a carpet store and dies.",
		answer2: "He gets the highest score and wins a prize.",
		answer3: "Rick jumps into the game and wins it for him.",
		answer4: "He shoots a goverment official and gets condemned to death.",
		correctAnswer: answer1	
	},	

	question7:
	{	actualQuestion: "The electricity in Rick's car is generated by ...?",
		answer1: "a battery purchased in an interplanetary store.",
		answer2: "solar power",
		answer3: "Rick jumps into the game and wins it for him.",
		answer4: "a microverse created by Rick.",
		correctAnswer: answer4	
	},

	question8:
	{	actualQuestion: "What song is playing when Rick and Arthricia go on a killing rampage during a purge?",
		answer1: "Shake it Off by Taylor Swift",
		answer2: "Harder, Better, Faster Stronger by Daft Punk",
		answer3: "I Feel Good by James Brown",
		answer4: "Feels Good by Tony! Toni! Ton√©!",
		correctAnswer: answer4
	},

	question9:
	{	actualQuestion: "What dimension does Rick claim to be from?",
		answer1: "A-42",
		answer2: "C-137",
		answer3: "C-157",
		answer4: "The Squanch dimension",
		correctAnswer: answer2
	},

	question10:
	{ 	actualQuestion: "What is the name of Morty's crush in Rick Potion Number 9?", 
		answer1: "Jennifer",
		answer2: "Amber",
		answer3: "Mark",
		answer4: "Jessica",
		correctAnswer: answer4	
	}
};

//Functions
//___________________________________________________________________

//Hides question section until start button is clicked
$("#questionSection").hide();

//Shows question section and timer when start button is clicked
$("#startButton").click(function(){
    $("#questionSection").show();
});

//Populates question and possible answer section

	$("#question").html(questions.question.actualQuestion);
	$("#answer1").html(questions.question1.answer1);
	$("#answer2").html(questions.question1.answer2);
	$("#answer3").html(questions.question1.answer3);
	$("#answer4").html(questions.question1.answer4);
	
	
//Timer counts down 10 seconds

    //  Sets timer to 10 seconds.
    var timer = 10;

    //  Variable that will hold our interval ID when we execute the "run" function
    var intervalId;


    //  The run function sets an interval that runs the decrement function once a second.
    function run() {
      intervalId = setInterval(decrement, 1000);
    }
    run();

    //  The decrement function.
    function decrement() {
      //  Decreases timer by one second.
      timer--;
      //  Shows the time in the #timer tag.
      $("#timer").html(timer);
      //  Once number hits zero...
      if (timer === 0) {
        //  ...run the stop function.
        stop();        
      }
    }

    //  The stop function
    function stop() {

      //  Clears our intervalId
      clearInterval(intervalId);
    }


//stops timer when answer is clicked
// $("#answer1").on("click", stop);
// $("#answer2").on("click", stop);
// $("#answer3").on("click", stop);
// $("#answer4").on("click", stop);



   //      //  Repopulate new set of questions and possible answers
   //  		$("#question").html(questions.question2.actualQuestion);
			// $("#answer1").html(questions.question2.answer1);
			// $("#answer2").html(questions.question2.answer2);
			// $("#answer3").html(questions.question2.answer3);
			// $("#answer4").html(questions.question2.answer4);
			// run();
			// timer = 10;